Love Don't Co$t A Thing but it pays to be yourself.
Love Don't Co$t a Thing is a comedy, drama, family film directed by Troy Byer.
A high school outcast pays a cheerleader to pose as his
girlfriend so he can be considered cool.
Alvin Johnson, played by Nick Cannon.
Paris Morgan, played by Christina Milian.
Walter Colley, played by Kenan Thompson.
Kenneth Warman, played by Kal Penn.
Clarence Johnson, played by Steve Harvey.
Vivian Johnson, played by Vanessa Bell Calloway.
Love Don't Cost a Thing (stylized as Love Don't Co$t a Thing) is a 2003 American teen comedy film
written and directed by Troy Byer and starring Nick Cannon and Christina Milian.
It also stars Steve Harvey, Kenan Thompson and Kal Penn.
The film is a remake of the 1987 film Can't Buy Me Love and takes on
its title from the Jennifer Lopez song of the same name.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.